RG 002:004, General Assembly Papers
Connecticut State Library
- 1913-1971, 1984-045
  - 1959
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health to Welfare (Box 403)
    - Unfinished Business - Roads, Rivers and Bridges to Water Resolutions (Box 404)
  - 1960
    - Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 404A)
  - 1961
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Senate and House Joint Resolutions (Box 405)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments; Constitutional Amendments; Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 406)
    - Public Acts, 1-129 (Box 407)
    - Public Acts, 130-239 (Box 408)
    - Public Acts, 240-330 (Box 409)
    - Public Acts, 331-429 (Box 410)
    - Public Acts, 430-509 (Box 411)
    - Public Acts, 510-575 (Box 412)
    - Public Acts, 576-606 (Box 413)
    - Special Acts, 1-185 (Box 414)
    - Special Acts, 186-320 (Box 415)
    - Special Acts, 321-411 (Box 416)
    - Special Acts, 412-421 (Box 417)
    - Rejected Bills - A-W (Box 418)
    - Unfinished Business - Agriculture; Appropriations (Box 419)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks to Constitutional Amendments (Box 420)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 421)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections; Federal Inter-Government Relations (Box 422)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 423)
    - Unfinished Business - Fish and Game; General Law (Box 424)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Judiciary (Box 425)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, 622-2801 (Box 426)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 427)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor; Liquor Control; Military Affairs (Box 428)
    - Unfinished Business - Penal Institution to Public Personnel (Box 429)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel; Public Utilities; Public Water (Box 430)
    - Unfinished Business - Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Rules; State Development (Box 431)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Water Resolutions; Flood Control (Box 432)
  - 1962
    - Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 432A)
  - 1963
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments; Constitutional Amendments (Box 433)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Special Session, June, Resolutions; Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 434)
    - Public Acts, 1-99 (Box 435)
    - Public Acts, 100-225 (Box 436)
    - Public Acts, 226-274 (Box 437)
    - Public Acts, 275-391 (Box 438)
    - Public Acts, 392-493 (Box 439)
    - Public Acts, 494-599 (Box 440)
    - Public Acts, 600-643 (Box 441)
    - Public Acts, 644-652 (Box 442)
    - Special Acts, 1-145 (Box 443)
    - Special Acts, 146-247 (Box 444)
    - Special Acts, 248-360 (Box 445)
    - Special Acts, 361-371 (Box 446)
    - Special Session, June 26, 1963 - Public Act 1 (Box 447)
    - Special Session, April 21, 1964 - Resolutions, House, House Joint, Senate, Senate Joint; Rejected Bills; Unfinished Business; Ruled Out of Order (Box 447)
    - Special Session, August 3, 1964 - Resolutions, House, House Joint, Senate, Senate Joint, Rejected, Unfinished Business (Box 447)
    - Unfinished Business - Agriculture; Appropriations (Box 448)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Constitutional Amendments (Box 449)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Elections (Box 450)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections; Federal and Inter-government Relations; Finance (Box 451)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 452)
    - Unfinished Business - Fish and Game; General Law (Box 453)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Incorporations (Box 454)
    - Unfinished Business- Insurance (Box 455)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Governmental Functions, Senate (Box 456)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Government Functions, House (Box 457)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary And Government Functions, House (Box 458)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor (Box 459)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control; Military Veterans Affairs; Penal Institutions; Public Health and Safety (Box 460)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel; Public Utilities (Box 461)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Welfare and Humane Institutions; Rivers, Roads and Bridge (Box 462)
    - Unfinished Business - Rivers, Roads and Bridges; Rules; State Development (Box 463)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Water Resolutions and Flood Control (Box 464)
  - 1964
    - Special Session, November 10 and April 21 (Box 465)
    - Initiation of 1964 (Box 465)
    - Local Legislation (Box 465)
  - 1965
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions (Box 466)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 467)
    - Public Acts, 1-124 (Box 468)
    - Public Acts, 125-275 (Box 469)
    - Public Acts, 276-350 (Box 470)
    - Public Acts, 351-449 (Box 471)
    - Public Acts, 450-494 (Box 472)
    - Public Acts, 495-574 (Box 473)
    - Public Acts, 575-630 (Box 474)
    - Special Acts, 1-211 (Box 475)
    - Special Acts, 212-299 (Box 476)
    - Special Acts, 300-379 (Box 477)
    - Special Session, December 13 (Box 478)
    - Unfinished Business - Agriculture; Appropriations (Box 479)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banks (Box 480)
    - Unfinished Business - Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Constitutional Amendments; Education (Box 481)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Elections (Box 482)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections; Finance (Box 483)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 484)
    - Unfinished Business - Fish and Game; General Law (Box 485)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Incorporations; Insurance (Box 486)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Governmental Functions (Box 487)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Governmental Functions (Box 488)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Governmental Functions (Box 489)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor (Box 490)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control; Military and Veterans Affairs; Penal Institutions; Public Health and Safety (Box 491)
    - Unfinished Business- Public Personnel (Box 492)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Utilities; Public Welfare and Humane Institutions; Rivers, Roads and Bridges (Box 493)
    - Unfinished Business - Rivers, Roads and Bridges; Rules; State Development (Box 494)
    - Unfinished Business - State Development; Transportation; Water Resolutions and Flood Control (Box 495)
    - Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 495A)
  - 1967
    - (Box 496)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions (Box 496)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 497)
    - Resolutions - House, House Joint, Senate, Senate Joint (Box 497)
    - Public Acts, 1-100 (Box 498)
    - Public Acts, 101-200 (Box 499)
    - Public Acts, 201-325 (Box 500)
    - Public Acts, 326-425 (Box 501)
    - Public Acts, 426-521 (Box 502)
    - Public Acts, 522-555 (Box 503)
    - Public Acts, 556-620 (Box 504)
    - Public Acts, 621-656 (Box 505)
    - Public Acts, 657-700 (Box 506)
    - Public Acts, 701-755 (Box 507)
    - Public Acts, 756-804 (Box 508)
    - Public Acts, 805-850 (Box 509)
    - Public Acts, 854-904 (Box 510)
    - Special Acts, 1-165 (Box 511)
    - Special Acts, 166-272 (Box 512)
    - Special Acts, 273-360 (Box 513)
    - Special Acts, 361-448 (Box 514)
    - Unfinished Business - Agriculture; Appropriations (Box 515)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Cities and Boroughs (Box 516)
    - Unfinished Business - Constitutional Amendments; Correction; Education, Senate (Box 517)
    - Unfinished Business -Education, House (Box 518)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections (Box 519)
    - Unfinished Business - Federal And Inter-government Relations; Finance (Box 520)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance; Fish and Game (Box 521)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 522)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 523)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Governmental Functions, 500-1510 (Box 524)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Governmental Functions, 2826-4156 (Box 525)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Governmental Functions, 4230 - 100,004 (Box 526)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Government Functions, 1613-2750 (Box 527)
    - Initiation of legislation (Box 528)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor (Box 529)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control, Military Veterans Affairs; Public Health and Safety (Box 530)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health and Safety; Public Personnel (Box 531)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel; Public Utilities (Box 532)
    - Unfinished Business - Pubic Welfare and Humane Institutions; Rivers, Roads and Bridges, Senate (Box 533)
    - Unfinished Business - Rivers, Roads and Bridges, House; Rules (Box 534)
    - Unfinished Business - State Development; Transportation (Box 535)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Water Resolutions and Flood Control (Box 536)
  - 1969
    - (Box 537)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments; Constitutional Amendments; Rejected Bills (Box 537)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 538)
    - Public Acts, 1-125 (Box 539)
    - Public Acts, 126-250 (Box 540)
    - Public Acts, 251-370 (Box 541)
    - Public Acts, 371-460 (Box 542)
    - Public Acts, 461-560 (Box 543)
    - Public Acts, 561-625 (Box 544)
    - Public Acts, 626-675 (Box 545)
    - Public Acts, 676-725 (Box 546)
    - Public Acts, 726-759 (Box 547)
    - Public Acts, 760-780 (Box 548)
    - Public Acts, 781-820 (Box 549)
    - Public Acts, 821-828 (Box 550)
    - Special Session, June 23 - Public Act (Box 550)
    - Special Acts, 1-140 (Box 551)
    - Special Acts, 141-240 (Box 552)
    - Special Acts, 241-295 (Box 553)
    - Special Session, June 23 - Special Acts (Box 553)
    - Unfinished Business - Agriculture; Appropriations (Box 554)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banks; Cities and Boroughs (Box 555)
    - Unfinished Business - Claims; Constitutional Amendments; Corrections; Education (Box 556)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Elections (Box 557)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections; Federal And Intergovernmental Relations; Finance (Box 558)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Senate; Finance, House (Box 559)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House (Box 560)
    - Unfinished Business - Fish and Game; General Law, Senate (Box 561)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 562)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Rights and Opportunities, Senate and House; Incorporations, Senate and House; Insurance and Real Estate, Senate and House; Judiciary and Governmental Functions, Senate (Box 563)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate 720-1575 (Box 564)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House 5054-6677, Joint Resolution 51 (Box 565)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House 6678-7411 (Box 566)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House 7500-8124 (Box 567)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House 8126-8655 (Box 568)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor; Legislation; Liquor Control (Box 569)
    - Unfinished Business - Military and Veterans Affairs; Public Health and Safety; Public Personnel, Senate (Box 570)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel, House (Box 571)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Utilities; Public Welfare (Box 572)
    - Unfinished Business - Rivers, Roads and Bridges; Rules (Box 573)
    - Unfinished Business - State Development, Senate, House 132-7460 (Box 574)
    - Unfinished Business - State Development, House 741-8656; Transportation (Box 575)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation; Water Resolutions and Flood Control (Box 576)
  - 1970
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House, House Joint, Senate, Senate Joint (Box 577)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Special Session, June 23, 1969 (Box 577)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Special Session, July 21, 1969 (Box 577)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Special Session, October 6, 1970 (Box 577)
    - (Box 578)
  - 1971
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Senate Resolutions, Special Sessions (Box 578)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - House Resolutions, Senate Resolutions, Special Session, Constitutional Amendments (Box 579)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 580)
    - Initiation of Local and General Assembly (Box 581)
    - Public Acts, 1-61 (Box 582)
    - Public Acts, 63-126 (Box 583)
    - Public Acts, 127-199 (Box 584)
    - Public Acts, 200-280 (Box 585)
    - Public Acts, 281-349 (Box 586)
    - Public Acts, 350-409 (Box 587)
    - Public Acts, 410-465 (Box 588)
    - Public Acts, 466-524 (Box 589)
    - Public Acts 525-575 (Box 590)
    - Public Acts, 576-640 (Box 591)
    - Public Acts, 641-679 (Box 592)
    - Public Acts, 700-750 (Box 593)
    - Public Acts, 751-799 (Box 594)
    - Public Acts, 800-834 (Box 595)
    - Public Acts, 835-855 (Box 596)
    - Public acts, 856-868 (Box 597)
    - Public Acts, 869-871 (Box 598)
    - Public Acts, 872 (Box 599)
    - Special Session, June 11 (Box 600)
    - Special Session, June - Public Acts 7-8 (Box 601)
    - Special Acts, 1-105 (Box 602)
    - Special Acts, 106-174 (Box 603)
    - Special Acts, 175-178 (Box 604)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 605)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 606)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 607)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House (Box 608)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House; Banks and Regulated Activities (Box 609)
    - Unfinished Business - Corrections, Welfare and Humane Institutions (Box 610)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, Senate; Education, House (Box 611)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House (Box 612)
    - Unfinished Business - Education, House; Elections (Box 613)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections (Box 614)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections; Environment, Senate (Box 615)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment; House (Box 616)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, Senate (Box 617)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House (Box 618)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House (Box 619)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance, House; Government Administration and Policy, House (Box 620)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy, House (Box 621)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy, Senate (Box 622)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, Senate (Box 623)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, Senate; General Law, House (Box 624)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law, House (Box 625)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Rights and Opportunities; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 626)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Judiciary, Senate 45-889 (Box 627)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate 890-1827 (Box 628)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary Special Session (Box 628)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House, 174-6212 (Box 629)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House, 6213-7494 (Box 630)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House, 7557-8779 (Box 631)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House, 8800-9260 (Box 632)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor (Box 633)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Liquor Control; Public Health and Safety, 128-5890 (Box 634)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health and Safety, 6015-9259 (Box 635)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel and Military Affairs, House 5111-7445 (Box 636)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel and Military Affairs, House 7448-9219, Senate 0070-1825 (Box 637)
    - Unfinished Business - Reapportionment; Rules; State and Urban Development, 167-6156 (Box 638)
    - Unfinished Business - State and Urban Development, 6309-9250; Transportation, House 249-6607 (Box 639)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, 6608-8898 (Box 640)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation, House 8899-9258; Senate 125-1755 (Box 641)
  - 1972
    - (Box 642)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Appointments; and Constitutional Amendments (Box 642)
    - Public Acts, 1-83 (Box 643)
    - Public Acts, 84-127 (Box 644)
    - Public Acts, 128-180 (Box 645)
    - Public Acts, 181-208 (Box 646)
    - Public Acts, 209-255 (Box 647)
    - Public Acts, 256-280 (Box 648)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate and House (Box 649)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks; Corrections; Education; Elections; and Environment (Box 650)
    - Special Session, May, 16 (Box 651)
    - Special Session, May 16 - Rejected Bills (Box 651)
    - Trailer Session, June 12 (Box 651)
    - Special Session, June 12 (Box 651)
    - Special Session, September 19 (Box 651)
    - Special Session, September - Appointments (Box 651)
    - Unfinished Business - Special Session, May 16; Special Session, June 21; Special Session, September 19 (Box 651)
    - Unfinished Business - Special Session, May 16, Public Health and Safety (Box 651)
    - Unfinished Business - Special Session, September 19, Appropriations; Finance; Judiciary; Transportation (Box 651)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 652)
    - Special Acts, 1-151 (Box 653)
    - Special Session, Special Act 1 (Box 653)
    - Public Acts, 281-295 (Box 654)
    - Special Sessions, May, June and September (Box 654)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 655)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Policy; Human Rights and Opportunities (Box 656)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 657)
    - Unfinished Business - Insurance and Real Estate; Labor (Box 658)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control; Public Health and Safety; Public Personnel and Military Affairs; Rules; State and Urban Development (Box 659)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 660)
  - 1973
    - (Box 661)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Senate Resolutions (Box 661)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Senate Session, June 12 (Box 661)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions (Box 661)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - House Resolutions (Box 662)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - House Joint - Resolutions (Box 663)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 664)
    - Public Acts, 1-75 (Box 665)
    - Public Acts, 76-124 (Box 666)
    - Public Acts, 125-165 (Box 667)
    - Public Acts, 166-220 (Box 668)
    - Public Acts, 221-275 (Box 669)
    - Public Acts, 276-340 (Box 670)
    - Public Acts, 341-375 (Box 671)
    - Public Acts, 376-426 (Box 672)
    - Public Acts, 427-465 (Box 673)
    - Public Acts, 466-530 (Box 674)
    - Public Acts, 531-567 (Box 675)
    - Public Acts, 568-598 (Box 676)
    - Public Acts, 599-620 (Box 677)
    - Public Acts, 621-650 (Box 678)
    - Public Acts, 651-670 (Box 679)
    - Public Acts, 671-682 (Box 680)
    - Special Acts, 1-60 (Box 681)
    - Special Acts, 61-130 (Box 682)
    - Special Acts, 131-143, excluding 140 (Box 683)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 683)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate and House (Box 684)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, House; Banks and Regulated Activities (Box 685)
    - Unfinished Business - Banks and Regulated Activities; Corrections and Humane Institutions (Box 686)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 687)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 688)
    - Unfinished Business - Education (Box 689)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment (Box 690)
    - Unfinished Business - Environment (Box 691)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections (Box 692)
    - Unfinished Business - Elections (Box 693)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 694)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 695)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 696)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 697)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 698)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law (Box 699)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy (Box 700)
    - Unfinished Business - Government Administration and Policy (Box 701)
    - Unfinished Business - Human Rights and Opportunities; Insurance and Real Estate (Box 702)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 703)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 704)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 705)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary (Box 706)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 707)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control; Legislative Management (Box 708)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health and Safety (Box 709)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Health and Safety (Box 710)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel and Military Affairs (Box 711)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel and Military Affairs (Box 712)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 713)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 714)
    - Unfinished Business - Transportation (Box 715)
  - 1974
    - (Box 716)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, Senate and Joint Resolutions, 1-76 (Box 716)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions, House and Joint Resolutions (Box 717)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Joint Resolutions (Box 718)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant -Resolutions of Reconvened June Session (Box 718)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 718)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 718)
    - Public Acts, 1-55 (Box 719)
    - Public Acts, 56-113 (Box 720)
    - Public Acts, 114-160 (Box 721)
    - Public Acts, 161-186 (Box 722)
    - Public Acts, 189-221 (Box 723)
    - Public Acts, 222-259 (Box 724)
    - Public Acts, 260-305 (Box 725)
    - Public Acts, 306-336 (Box 726)
    - Public Acts, 337-345 (Box 727)
    - Special Acts, 1-53 (Box 728)
    - Special Acts, 54-119 (Box 729)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 730)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 730)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations (Box 731)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations; Banks and Regulated Activities; Corrections, Welfare and Humane Institutions (Box 732)
    - Unfinished Business - Education; Elections; Environment; Finance (Box 733)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 734)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 735)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law; Government Administration and Policy; Human Rights and Opportunities; Insurance; Judiciary (Box 736)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary; Labor (Box 737)
    - Unfinished Business - Legislative Management; Liquor Control; Public Health and Safety; Public Personnel and Military Affairs (Box 738)
    - Unfinished Business - State and Urban Development; Transportation (Box 739)
  - 1975
    - (Box 740)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Senate and Senate Joint Resolutions (Box 740)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - House Resolutions 1-248 (Box 741)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - House and House Joint Resolutions (Box 742)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 743)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Special Session, July (Box 743)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Constitutional Amendments (Box 744)
    - Special Session, July and December (Box 744)
    - Public Acts, 1-47 (Box 744)
    - Public Acts, 49-108 (Box 745)
    - Public Acts, 109-165 (Box 746)
    - Public Acts, 166-213 (Box 747)
    - Public Acts, 214-268 (Box 748)
    - Public Acts, 269-310 (Box 749)
    - Public Acts, 311-360 (Box 750)
    - Public Acts, 361-399 (Box 751)
    - Public Acts, 400-425 (Box 752)
    - Public Acts, 426-470 (Box 753)
    - Public Acts, 471-486 (Box 754)
    - Public Acts, 487-524 (Box 755)
    - Public Acts, 525-558 (Box 756)
    - Public Acts, 559-570 (Box 757)
    - Public Acts, 571-597 (Box 758)
    - Public Acts, 598-626 (Box 759)
    - Public Acts, 627-644 (Box 760)
    - Special Session, Public Act 1 (Box 760)
    - Special Acts, 1-44 (Box 761)
    - Special Acts, 45-101 (Box 762)
    - Special Session, Special Act 1 (Box 762)
    - Rejected Bills (Box 763)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate (Box 764)
    - Unfinished Business - Appropriations, Senate, House (Box 765)